Inventory of the Lelan Flor Sillin papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Lelan Flor Sillin papers
1952-1985
99021
Hoover Institution Archives
104 manuscript boxes (41.6 linear feet)
Speeches and writings, correspondence, minutes, reports, studies, manuals, and meeting materials relating to the electric and nuclear power industries and to environmental and energy policy in the United States, especially to activities of the Institute of Nuclear Power Operations, Northeast Utilities, Atomic Industrial Forum, Inc., and the Electric Power Research Institute.
Sillin, Lelan Flor, 1918-1997
Access
Collection stored off site; a minimum of two days notice is required for use. Boxes may be requested through Stanford's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1999.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
Lelan Flor Sillin was the chief executive officer and chairman of the board for Northeast Utilities from 1961 to 1983, and director and chairman for the Institute of Nuclear Power Operations from 1980 to 1985.
Scope and Content of Collection
Speeches and writings, correspondence, minutes, reports, studies, manuals, and meeting materials relating to the electric and nuclear power industries and to environmental and energy policy in the United States, as well as to activities of the Institute of Nuclear Power Operations, Northeast Utilities, Atomic Industrial Forum, Inc., and the Electric Power Research Institute.
Atomic Industrial Forum.; Electric Power Research Institute.; Institute of Nuclear Power Operations (U.S.); Electric industries--United States.; Energy policy--United States.; Environmental policy--United States.; Nuclear energy--United States.
- Correspondence, 1952-1977
  - Personal correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 36: 1-7, Box-folder 35: 8-9)
    Scope and Contents note
    A sketch of Lelan F. Sillin that was used in a publication can be found in the January of 1968 folder (35: 9).
  - Congratulatory correspondence sent, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - Congratulatory correspondence received, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - Aspen Institute Group, 1977 (Box-folder 97: 4)
  - Bechtel Corporation, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 95: 3)
  - Common Cause, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 28: 13)
  - Community Film Workshop Council, 1968 (Box-folder 95: 5)
  - New England Energy Policy Organization, 1974 (Box-folder 96: 6)
  - New York institutions, 1957-1971
    - New York State Council on Economic Education, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 33: 1)
    - New York State Electric and Gas Corporation, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 32: 13)
    - New York State Electric Power Committee, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 32: 12)
    - New York State Graduate Science Center, 1963 (Box-folder 32: 11)
    - New York State Traffic Safety Council, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 33: 2)
    - New York State Utilities Executives Conference, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 33: 3)
    - New York Telephone Company Questionnaire, 1958 (Box-folder 32: 14)
    - New York Telephone Company Rate Case, 1957 (Box-folder 32: 15)
    - Vassar Brothers Hospital, 1957-1971 (Box-folder 33: 4-5)
    - Vassar College, 1967 (Box-folder 32: 10)
  - Professor A.J.G. Priest re Electric Power Reliability Act, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 79: 6)
  - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1963-1973
    - 1963-1973 (Box-folder 60: 5)
    - Electric Utility Industry Task Force on the Environment, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 61: 1-6, Box-folder 62: 1-4)
    - Working file regarding Rockefeller luncheon, 1966 October 21 (Box-folder 62: 5-6)
    - Citizens' Advisory Committee on Recreation and Natural Beauty, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 62: 7-8)
  - Society of Gas Lighting Membership, 1964-1973 (Box-folder 95: 7)
  - Peter Stern, 1968 (Box-folder 59: 15-16)
  - Various companies, 1952-1974 (Box 8)
    - Abercrombie and Fitch, 1960-1971
    - American Bar Association, 1952-1973
    - American Express, 1972-1974
    - American Judicature Society, 1961-1971
    - Atomic Energy Commission Clearance, 1955-1968
    - Brooks Brothers, 1956-1973
    - Camp Abnaki of the Young Men's Christian Association, 1955-1960
    - Central Hudson Gas and Electric bills to Mr. Sillin
    - Milton Alley, Agway Quality Products, 1959-1970
- Speeches, 1968-1983
  - Speeches, 1972 January-1976 October (Box-folder 2: 1-7)
    For the most part these speeches were given while Sillin was the president of Northeast Utilities to fellow board members, bankers, lawyers, and colleagues. The speeches generally pertained to energy and the environment.
  - Collected speeches by L. F. Sillin, 1968-1983 (Box-folder 104: 1-5)
  - Remarks before New England Conference of Public Utilities Commissioners, 1977 (Box-folder 97: 7)
  - University of Rochester Labratory for Laser Energies cornerstone ceremonies remarks and information, 1976 (Box-folder 97: 6)
- Awards, 1960s
  - Red Bull Motor Inn All Electric Award, 1965 March 25 (Box-folder 88: 5)
  - Reddy Kilowatts Annual Report Awards, 1967 April 17 (Box-folder 88: 6)
  - Safety Achievement Award Dinner, 1960 March 30 (Box-folder 88: 10)
- Miscellaneous Meeting Materials and Minutes, 1965, 1969-1977, 1984-1985
  - Bechtel Power Corporation, Electric Utility Industry meeting, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 70: 10)
  - Energy Research Group meeting minutes, 1974 July (Box-folder 94: 3-4)
  - Greater Hartford Process, Inc. meeting minutes, correspondence, documents, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 96: 4)
  - Hammonasset School meeting, 1984 December 3 (Box-folder 84: 5)
  - NAACP Connecticut meeting minutes, correspondence, documents, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 96: 3)
  - NAEC meeting material, 1977 June 9 (Box-folder 97: 3)
  - Regional Chamber of Commerce Council meeting, 1965 September 22 (Box-folder 88: 7)
- Reports, Research Materials, and Other Documents, 1965-1977, 1984
  - Assorted remarks, documents, minutes, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 97: 1)
  - Documents regarding contributions from Mr. Sillin, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 7: 3-4)
  - EHV transmission lines, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 84: 6)
  - Electric Council of New England documents, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 95: 6)
  - Electric Power Reliability Act of 1967, 1967 April-1968 May (Box-folder 81: 1-3, Box-folder 79: 7-10, Box-folder 80: 1-7)
  - Manpower for the electric industry, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 32: 1)
  - Material for West Coast trip, 1971 (Box-folder 98: 5)
  - Materials pertaining to November 12-13 meetings in D.C. regarding nuclear power initiatives, 1975 (Box-folder 97: 9)
  - National Economic Research Association documents, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 96: 5)
  - National Electric Reliability Council documents and reports, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 96: 7)
  - President Carter energy proposal documents, 1977 (Box-folder 97: 5, Box-folder 98: 6)
  - Publications and reports, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 34: 10, Box-folder 35: 1-2)
    Most of these publications and reports involve the environment or the utilities industry and the environment. They are published by various organizations.
  - "Regional Reliability Council Long Range Coordinated Bulk Power Supply Programs,", 1984 April 1 (Box-folder 88: 12)
  - Reports, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 28: 3-9)
  - Vassar College study, 1967 (Box-folder 29: 10)
  - Untitled (miscellany), 1971 (Box-folder 27: 17)
- Advanced Energy Dynamics, Inc. (AED) File, 1983-1985
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 28: 11)
  - Board meetings, 1983 (Box-folder 28: 10, Box-folder 26: 7-9)
  - Business plan, 1981 (Box-folder 28: 12)
  - Expenses, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 73: 17)
- Arthur D. Little, Inc. (ADL) File, 1981-1985
  - General correspondence, undated (Box-folder 13: 3-6)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 87: 2-4)
  - Correspondence from Sillin to ADL, 1983 August (Box-folder 25: 4)
  - Correspondence from ADL to Sillin, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 25: 5)
  - Board of Directors, undated (Box-folder 11: 4-6, Box-folder 13: 1-2, Box-folder 12: 1-8)
  - Annual Board of Directors meeting, 1983 March 31 (Box-folder 27: 5)
  - Compensation and board meetings, 1983 (Box-folder 27: 1-4)
  - Directors' questionnaires, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 74: 1)
  - Compensation Committee meeting, 1983 (Box-folder 25: 8-9, Box-folder 26: 1-2)
  - Monthly financial reports, 1983 (Box-folder 26: 3)
  - Strategic Facilities Planning Project for Acorn Park, 1982 (Box-folder 25: 7)
  - Acorn Park Master Plan report, 1983 July 18 (Box-folder 26: 4)
- Atomic Industrial Forum, Inc. (AIF) File, 1968-1975, 1982-1984
  - AIF, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 29: 10)
  - General correspondence, undated (Box-folder 7: 5-6, Box-folder 9: 1-10, Box-folder 10: 1-6)
  - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 26: 5, Box-folder 89: 4)
  - Correspondence to the White House, 1975 (Box-folder 91: 8)
  - Board of Directors' correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 91: 3-5)
  - Executive Committee correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 91: 6-7)
  - Board of Directors, undated (Box-folder 10: 7-10, Box-folder 11: 1-3, Box-folder 25: 1-3)
  - Executive Committee and Board of Directors meetings, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 89: 5-11, Box-folder 91: 1-2, Box-folder 90: 1-12)
  - Executive Committee meeting, 1983 September 27 (Box-folder 24: 9)
  - Meeting with the New York Times, 1973 June 7 (Box-folder 92: 2)
  - Public Affairs and Information Committee, 1983 (Box-folder 27: 7)
  - Senior Management Policy Committee on reactor licensing, 1973 (Box-folder 92: 1)
  - Annual report, 1983 October 21 (Box-folder 24: 8)
  - Annual conferences, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 91: 9-11)
  - Strategic plan, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 25: 6)
  - Periodicals, 1983 (Box-folder 26: 6)
  - Executive compensation and employee benefits, 1983 (Box-folder 27: 6)
  - Superior Court cases, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 27: 8)
  - Nuclear ship liability, 1974 December 16 (Box-folder 92: 3)
- Carolina Power and Light Company File, 1983
  - Correspondence from Sillin, 1983 (Box-folder 24: 7)
  - Board meetings, 1983
    - 1983 March (Box-folder 24: 5-6)
    - 1983 May 1-6 (Box-folder 24: 4)
    - 1983 September 21 (Box-folder 23: 9)
    - 1983 December 21 (Box-folder 23: 7)
  - Committee on Forecasting System Development and Finance meeting, 1983 September 13 (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Financial information, 1983 (Box-folder 23: 6)
  - Executive management resources review, 1983 July 28 (Box-folder 24: 3)
  - Sillin's trip to Carolina Power and Light, 1983 December 5-6 (Box-folder 23: 8)
  - To Raleigh, North Carolina, 1983 July 27 (Box-folder 24: 2)
- Central Hudson Gas and Electric File, 1960-1970
  - Blackout, 1969 November (Box-folder 79: 4-5)
  - Electric Power Reliability Act, 1965-1968
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder 73: 11)
    - Correspondence regarding recommended legislation, 1968 (Box-folder 73: 9)
    - Executive Steering and Legal Liaison Committee correspondence, 1965 (Box-folder 73: 2)
    - Directors' meeting notes regarding the Electric Power Reliability Bill, 1967 (Box-folder 73: 8)
    - Electric Power Reliability Bill, 1967 December (Box-folder 73: 4)
    - Electric Power Reliability Act amendment booklet, 1968 (Box-folder 72: 1)
    - Questions to the Federal Power Commission, 1967 September 22 (Box-folder 73: 3)
    - Public Service Commission, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 73: 1)
    - State Utilities Commission information, 1967 September 11 (Box-folder 72: 2)
    - National utilities legislation, 1968 (Box-folder 72: 3-5)
    - Memorandum concerning the Federal Power Commission Electric Power Reliability Act of 1967, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 71: 10)
    - Addendum to the memorandum concerning the Federal Power Commission Electric Power Reliability Act of 1967 (Box-folder 71: 11)
    - Report to the President of the Federal Power Commission, "Prevention of Power Failures," Volumes I and II, 1967 July (Box-folder 72: 9)
    - Report on remaining cases, 1965 June 3 (Box-folder 72: 6)
    - Second report on remaining cases, 1965 October 8 (Box-folder 72: 7)
    - Reports of proceedings of hearings held before the Subcommittee on Communication and Power of the Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce to amend the Federal Power Act, 1967 December 5 (Box-folder 73: 7)
    - Transcripts of proceedings for the Committee on Commerce Hearings on the Electric Power Reliability Bill, 1967 December 20-21 (Box-folder 73: 5-6)
    - Chairman's request for further instructions regarding Atlantic City et al. v. Worthington et al., 1965 September 27 (Box-folder 72: 8)
    - Addendum to Investigation of Northeast Power Failure, Part 2, 1967 January 23 (Box-folder 72: 10)
    - Federal Power Commission article in Yale Law Journal, 1967 October 18 (Box-folder 73: 10)
  - Herald Tribune Fresh Air Fund Camp, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 71: 8)
  - Hudson River Basin Compact, 1968 January 15 (Box-folder 71: 7)
  - Hudson River Conservation Society, Inc., 1960-1969 (Box-folder 71: 6)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission, 1967 (Box-folder 71: 5)
  - Hudson Valley Opportunities Industrialization Center, Inc., 1967 November 23 (Box-folder 71: 4)
  - National Rivers and Harbors Congress, 1965 March (Box-folder 71: 9)
  - Public Service Commission meetings with Chairman Lundy, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 79: 3)
- Citizen's Advisory Committee on Environmental Quality (CACEQ) File, 1969-1974
  - CACEQ, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 28: 1-2, Box-folder 27: 9-16)
  - General, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 93: 1, Box-folder 92: 6-7)
  - Meeting minutes, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 94: 1-2, Box-folder 93: 4-7)
  - Energy Subcommittee, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 92: 4-5)
  - Public Utilities and Publications Committee, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 93: 3)
  - President's energy message, 1973 April 24 (Box-folder 92: 6)
- Edison Electric Institute File, 1971-1976
  - 1971 (Box-folder 29: 3)
  - 1972 (Box-folder 29: 4)
  - Board of Directors correspondence, 1971 July-December (Box-folder 29: 6-9)
  - Committee on Occupational Safety and Health Act, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 29: 5)
  - Policy Committee on Atomic Power, 1972 January (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - Policy Committee on Research documents and correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 97: 8)
  - President's Conference, 1972 December (Box-folder 73: 12)
  - Edison Award, undated (Box-folder 29: 2)
- Elderhostel File, 1983-1984
  - Elderhostel correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 69: 3)
  - Board meeting, 1984 October 30 (Box-folder 86: 13, Box-folder 87: 1)
  - Orientation and board meeting of Elderhostel, 1983 October 25-26 (Box-folder 69: 2)
  - Meeting with Bill Wasch of Elderworks, 1984 November 5 (Box-folder 86: 12)
- Electric Power Research Institute (EPRI) File, 1972-1979, 1983
  - Action papers, 1974-1977
    The Action Papers are numbered and dated, though not always correspondingly. The papers are in numerical order although the series is not complete and many papers are missing.
    - 74-1 through 74-45, 1974 January-September (Box-folder 49: 1-5)
    - 75-1 through 75-65, 1974 December-1975 October (Box-folder 49: 6-10)
    - 75-68 through 75-77, 1975 October (Box-folder 50: 1-2)
    - 76-2 through 76-57, 1976 January-November (Box-folder 50: 3-10)
    - 77-14 through 77-20, 1977 April (Box-folder 50: 11)
  - Advisory Council correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 66: 5-7)
  - Board of Directors' correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 66: 8-11)
  - Research and Development correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 68: 5-6)
  - Advisory Council meeting minutes, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 68: 1-4)
  - Board of Directors' annual meeting, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 67: 1-4)
  - Board of Directors' meeting minutes and documents, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 66: 1-7, Box-folder 63: 1-9, Box-folder 65: 1-10, Box-folder 64: 1-11)
  - Aspen workshop, 1976 August 16-20 (Box-folder 69: 1)
- Federal Power Commission File, 1966-1970
  - Distribution Technical Advisory Committee, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 81: 5)
  - Executive Advisory Committee meeting minutes, 1962-1971 (Box-folder 81: 6-12, Box-folder 82: 1-12, Box-folder 83: 1-12, Box-folder 84: 1-4)
  - Generation Technical Advisory Committee, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 81: 4)
  - Regional Advisory Committees, 1967 (Box-folder 32: 2)
  - East Central Regional Advisory Committee, 1969 (Box-folder 32: 3)
  - Northeast Regional Advisory Committee, 1968 (Box-folder 32: 6)
  - South Central Regional Advisory Committee, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 32: 7)
  - Southeast Regional Advisory Committee, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 32: 8)
  - West Central Regional Advisory Committee, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 32: 9)
  - West Regional Advisory Committee, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 32: 5)
  - Rulemaking, Docket R-302, 1966 (Box-folder 32: 4)
- Fuel Cell Users Group File, 1979-1985
  - General correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 70: 5-9)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 85: 8-10)
  - Committee correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 69: 4-10)
  - Department of Energy (DOE) correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 85: 11)
  - DOE uranium enrichment correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 85: 12)
  - Fuel Cell Board correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 68: 7-9)
  - Gas-cooled reactor correspondence, 1984 February (Box-folder 86: 6)
  - Tokyo Electric Power Company correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 86: 7)
  - United Technologies Corporation correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 86: 8)
  - Fuel Cell Board, 1983 May 25 (Box-folder 59: 13)
  - Board meeting, 1983 August 9 (Box-folder 70: 2)
  - Meeting, 1984 December 4 (Box-folder 86: 5)
  - Meeting of the Directorate, 1983 November 6-7 (Box-folder 70: 1)
  - Meeting in Washington D.C., 1984 May 25 (Box-folder 86: 4)
  - Meeting with Robert Gray of energy transition, 1984 August 3 (Box-folder 86: 3)
  - Meeting with Mr. Longenecker from the Department of Energy, 1984 February 10 (Box-folder 85: 13)
  - Meeting with Messieurs Maxwell and Wood, 1984 July 23 (Box-folder 86: 9)
  - Meetings with Bill Podolny, 1983 June-August (Box-folder 86: 11)
  - Meeting with Messieurs Wood, Maxwell, and Curry, 1983 December 1 (Box-folder 85: 7)
  - Miscellaneous meeting files, 1984 (Box-folder 85: 5)
  - Edison Electric Chief Executive Officer conference in Scottsdale, Arizona, 1984 January 11-13 (Box-folder 85: 6)
  - Sproull and Laboratory for Laser Energetics presentation, 1983 October 12 (Box-folder 86: 10)
  - Ceremony, 1982 October 21 (Box-folder 70: 3)
  - Information packet, 1982 (Box-folder 70: 4)
  - Fuel Cell report to Management Committee, 1983 July (Box-folder 59: 14)
  - The Uranium Enrichment Enterprise: A Strategic Review, 1983 December (Box-folder 86: 1)
  - DOE uranium enrichment purchase order, 1984 (Box-folder 86: 2)
- Hartford Steam Boiler File, 1978-1985
  - General correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 59: 12)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 43: 14-15)
  - Board of Directors' meetings, 1978-1980 (Box 6)
    - 1978 August
    - 1979 August-September
    - 1979 October 22
    - 1979 December
    - 1980 January 28
    - 1980 January 25
    - 1980 March 24
    - 1980 April 15
    - 1980 June 2
    - 1980 June 8-12
    - 1980 June 23
  - Board of Directors' meetings, 1983 (Box-folder 59: 1-10, Box-folder 58: 9-12)
  - Board meetings, 1984
    - 1984 January 23 (Box-folder 43: 2)
    - Executive committee in Mr. Wilde's conference room, 1984 February 13 (Box-folder 43: 3)
    - 1984 February 27 (Box-folder 43: 4)
    - 1984 March 26 (Box-folder 43: 5)
    - Annual stockholder's meeting, 1984 April 17 (Box-folder 43: 6)
    - Annual meeting, 1984 May 29 (Box-folder 43: 7)
    - 1984 June 25 (Box-folder 43: 8)
    - 1984 July 23 (Box-folder 43: 9)
    - 1984 August 27 (Box-folder 43: 10)
    - 1984 September 24 (Box-folder 43: 11)
    - 1984 October 22 (Box-folder 43: 12)
    - 1984 November 26 (Box-folder 43: 13)
  - Director's retainer fee, undated (Box-folder 43: 16)
  - Short term incentive plan, 1982 December 27 (Box-folder 59: 11)
- Institute of Nuclear Power Operations (INPO) File, 1979-1984
  - General correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 18: 4, Box-folder 34: 6-9)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 88: 1-3, Box-folder 87: 5-12)
  - Correspondence relating to Northeast Utilities, 1983 (Box-folder 23: 1-3, Box-folder 18: 5-7)
  - Correspondence relating to the NRC, 1983 (Box-folder 19: 1)
  - Correspondence to the NRC, 1981 (Box-folder 88: 4)
  - Advisory Council correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 58: 1)
  - Advisory Council correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 42: 6)
  - Board of Directors' correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 56: 11)
  - Board of Directors' correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 40: 6-8, Box-folder 43: 1)
  - Executive Committee correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 22: 11, Box-folder 17: 4)
  - Point of Contact correspondence, 1983-1985
    - Survey of Nuclear-Related Occupational Employment in U.S. Electric Utilities, 1983 (Box-folder 22: 3)
    - Workshops, 1983 October (Box-folder 36: 9)
    - 1984-1985 (Box-folder 22: 1-2, Box-folder 21: 12)
  - Advisory Council meeting, 1983 March 22 (Box-folder 58: 2-5)
  - Advisory Council meeting, 1984 (Box-folder 42: 3-5)
  - Advisory Council and Board of Directors' meeting, 1980 February 12-13 (Box-folder 14: 8)
  - Annual meeting, 1983 March 23 (Box-folder 58: 6)
  - Annual meeting and Board and Executive meetings, 1983 March 23 (Box-folder 36: 8)
  - Annual meeting, 1984 March 2-4 (Box-folder 78: 6)
  - Board of Directors' conference calls, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 13: 7-12)
    - 1979 November 14
    - 1980 June 10
    - 1980 July 9
    - 1980 September 11
    - 1980 October 8
    - 1980 December 10
  - Board of Directors' conference call, 1984 April 18 (Box-folder 39: 11)
  - Board of Directors' meetings, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 14: 1-6)
    - 1979 December 6
    - 1980 January 9
    - 1980 April 9
    - 1980 May 14
    - 1980 August 13
    - 1980 November 12
  - Board of Directors' meetings, 1983 (Box-folder 57: 1-5)
  - Board of Directors' meetings, 1984 (Box-folder 39: 10, Box-folder 40: 2-3, Box-folder 41: 1-4)
  - Board members meeting with the United States Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC) Commissioners in Washington, D.C., 1980 March 11 (Box-folder 14: 7)
  - Executive Committee meetings and conference calls, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 22: 4-7, Box-folder 21: 1-3, Box 16, Box-folder 17: 1-3)
  - NRC related meetings, 1984
    - Meeting with Chairman Palladino and the Nuclear Regulatory Commissioners, 1984 September 12 (Box-folder 22: 8)
    - Meetings with the NRC and staff, undated (Box-folder 22: 9)
    - Meeting with the NRC in Washington D.C., 1984 September 12 (Box-folder 21: 10)
    - Trip to INPO - NRC visit, 1984 (Box-folder 22: 10)
    - Various meetings regarding the NRC debriefing, annual report, Chief Executive Officer conference, etc., 1984 September-October (Box-folder 21: 7)
  - Nuclear Utility Management and Resources Council (NUMARC) executive meeting, undated (Box-folder 76: 11)
  - Meeting with Congressman Dingell, 1984 September 29 (Box-folder 41: 5)
  - Meeting with New York financial community, 1983 February 11 (Box-folder 38: 2-4)
  - Meeting with the Nuclear Regulatory Commission in Washington, D.C., 1983 March 11 (Box-folder 38: 1)
  - Meeting with Jack Svanh, President's Advisory Council at the White House, 1984 September 20 (Box-folder 21: 6)
  - Meeting with Senator Lowell Weicker, 1984 February 23 (Box-folder 40: 5)
  - INPO at Edison Electric Institute, CEO Conference regarding the Construction Project Evaluation Program, 1983 January (Box-folder 37: 10)